modulates.com 2017-11-29

# Privacy Policy | Modulates.com

Modulates is an owner of the information collected on this site. Information collected is in two distinct categories:  Member information and aggregated Web User information. This portion of Modulates' privacy policy applies only to Publishers or Affiliates, not to general web users.

Members of Modulates or related networks include publishers and advertisers involved in advertising transactions. Member information collected includes personally identifiable information that is necessary to conduct business, such as name, phone number, email address, social security number, and/or tax ID number. Payments made to and from Modulates require the provision of and certain collection of personally identifiable information, which may include bank account information and credit card numbers. All information is collected, modified, and stored in a password protected environment. This information is used for the purposes of service, media delivery, contact, billing and accounts payable. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to non-Modulates related entities and affiliates, unless and except as provided for herein. All information collection is explicit, voluntary, and manually entered by the Publisher, Affiliate, Member or its agent. ****

**a. Identifiers and Cookies.**

A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored on a computer for the purpose of identifying that browser during interaction on websites. Cookies may be used to store items such as identifiers and user preferences. A website may set a cookie to the browser if the browser's preferences allow it. A browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has set, not those set by other websites.

When a consumer responds to or views an Internet advertisement served by Modulates (such as through third-party Web sites or email solicitation) or visits the Modulates site, a Cookie and/or gif file is sent to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the end user's Internet browser. 

These Cookies provide Modulates with information for the purpose of paying third-parties commissions when an Internet user clicks on a link, creates a lead, or makes a purchase on an advertiser's Web site. If the Internet user re-visits the advertiser's site directly, Modulates may continue to track the user's activities (excluding PII) on the advertiser's site and reward the third-party Web site that referred the user. We may use Cookies to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, as well as to determine the frequency of display. 

Modulates may use cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

Access your information when you sign in so we can provide you with customized content.

Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Modulates.

Control the delivery of a series of advertisements to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement. We also may use Internet browsing and online purchase data associated with an anonymous identifier to develop a predictive statistical user profile of the end user's needs and interests. 

Optimize and personalize your experience and allow Modulates to monitor log-ins and site traffic patterns. We record the IP address of members at each login, and this information is part of a secure database and is password protected.

We reserve the right to retain all ad delivery and reporting data as long as Modulates finds it is reasonably necessary for accounting and audit purposes. 

**b. Affiliate Websites and Limitation on Liability.**

Our rights and obligations with regard to Affiliate information are solely defined by our contract with that Affiliate and are solely to that Affiliate, and we do not, through these policies or otherwise, make any promise or undertake any obligation directly to any user of any Affiliate's website with regard to any use or disclosure of that information. Each Affiliate is solely responsible for establishing its own privacy policy, communicating that policy to the users of its website and ensuring that any access to, processing, storage and use by Modulates, in accordance with the applicable Agreement, of any data about those users is consistent with that Affiliate's own privacy policy. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Modulates expressly disclaims any obligation or liability to any user of any Affiliate's website of any nature, including with regard to any data about that user that Modulates obtains, processes, stores, uses or discloses.

**c. No Information Collected from Children.**

**Modulates will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If Modulates obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, Modulates has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. Modulates has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”).**

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to participate in and monitor their online activity.  If a parent or guardian believes that Modulates has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact [http://www.modulates.com/contact-us](http://www.modulates.com/contact-us.php) and we will use our best efforts to remove the information from our records.
